这里是刷新按钮在
Here's the code for the Refresh button in
forecastfragment.xml菜单文件里的代码  我们想让它
the forecastfragment menu XML file. We want it to
出现在更多菜单里  所以我们把它的showAsAction属性设置
appear in the overflow menu, so we set showAsAction
成为永不（never）  我们也声明了一个字符串  你可以
as never. We also declare the string. You can
在string.xml文件中找到这个字符串  这个文件
find the string here in the strings.xml file, which
存放在res目录下面的valuse文件夹中
is located in the values folder, which is in
你可以把你的string.xml文件里面的字符串翻译
the res folder. You can get your strings.xml file
成为不同的语言  这样会在res目录下添加额外的values文件夹
translated into different languages. This adds additional values folders,
比如  你会看到
under Res. For example, you would have
values-es  这是西班牙语  values-fr  这是法语  然后
values-es, for Spanish, values-fr for French. And
在每一个values文件夹里面
within each of those values folders, you
都要有一个strings.xml文件  这个文件里面
would have a strings.xml file, which would
包含的是翻译为相应语言的字符串
contain the localized strings for that language.
由于翻译有时候是花钱的  给你一个专业的
Since translation does cost money, as a
提示  你可以把那些
pro tip, you can mark strings that
你不想翻译的字符串标记为translatable=false  举个例子
you don't need translated using translatable=false. For example,
如果字符串是一个合适的名字  或者是仅仅为了调试而存在的
if it's a proper name or if it's for debugging like this one,
那你可以告诉你的翻译员  可以忽略这些字符串的翻译
then you can indicate to the translator that they can skip over this strings